Hey everybody, thanks for joining us. I
don't know why Ted's silent all of a
sudden.
>> Oh, there we go. I was on the delay. Go
ahead, John.
>> No, I was just saying hi to everyone.
You know, we we uh get ready for these
uh these podcasts in the same way every
day. God bless Ted because
he does most of the work and I just uh
show up at at 5 and and we have a nice
conversation. But there was so much news
again today, just like last Friday.
I thought, well, you know, I'm going to
try to get on top of it. I was actually
busy today. Did a couple of other
podcasts
and I haven't been able to catch up on
the news the last couple of hours until
Ted sent me the text of what he wanted
to talk about. It's like, oh my god, how
did I miss all this news in the last two
hours?
>> It's It's never a dull moment. Ever.
Ever.
>> Outrageous. ridiculous.
>> Where should where should we be? Where
should we start? I mean, I'm kind of
thinking a lot about the uh visa
denials.
>> Yeah.
>> For uh Makmoud Abbas and so on.
>> Yeah. I think Donald Trump was very
angry today and I think that the
afternoon's news is showing that not
only did the White House State
Department order that visas be denied
the to the Palestinian delegation to the
United Nations,
not despite the fact that Palestine is
going to be recognized by a host of
Western countries, but probably because
Palestine is going to be recognized by a
host of western countries. Now,
historically,
the um the United States has approved
everybody's visas, right? I mean, every
year the president of Iran comes or at
least the foreign minister of Iran. Uh
Muamar Gaddafi used to come every year
for the general assembly. Fidel Castro
used to come for the general assembly.
The leaders of the Soviet Union used to
come every year.
>> Yes, they did. But now all of a sudden
we don't want Palestinians in our
country, especially Palestinian leaders
to whom we donate millions of dollars to
keep them going administratively.
>> I mean, it must be a little confusing,
right? I mean, these aren't these aren't
Hamas officials. These this is the
Palestinian Authority, Makmoud Abbas.
Um, they're, as you said, John, we
support them. We finance them. We prop
them up. Um, and we recogn, you know, we
we get along with them. These are the
people who we call them and they call
us. And the Palestinian Authority kind
of is like a Vichy organization as far
as the Palestinians are concerned. They
cooperate with the IDF and with the
Israelis on everything. They let they
tell the Israelis, "Hey, there's uh, you
know, some radicals here. Come and get
them."
>> Yes. Yes. Exactly. Listen, whether we
think the Palestinian Authority is
corrupt or not, it's corrupt. We all
>> sure.
>> But they're the guys that we deal with.
They're the guys that our diplomats in
Jerusalem deal with every single day,
but now all of a sudden they're not
permitted to come to the uh to the
United Nations. It it makes zero sense
to me other than to be just provocative,
provocatively anti-Palestinian.
>> Well, it sounds like to me like this was
just a uh a soop to the Israelis, right?
Like agree.
>> The Israelis said like um you know,
they're they're they're plotting and
scheming here. Um they knew that the UN
General Assembly obviously it's been
scheduled for many well it's every year
every year and so they knew it was
coming and uh they decided okay we're
just gonna we're just going to be dicks
right I mean basically
>> and Ted you know when when the United
Nations was created in the 1940s
the deal was the deal that the United
States made with the rest of the world
is that everybody was free to come to
the United Nations
>> right
>> right there are North Korean diplomats
in New York
>> who are assigned to the United Nations.
>> Right.
>> Right. Everybody's welcome because
everybody's represented. It's the world
body. It's where we're supposed to go to
make peace.
>> John, to go even further than that, like
even nonrecognized states that were
enemy adversaries of the United States
just because the UN was here in New
York, uh they could hang out. So, yeah.
>> Uh you know, there was a Taliban
representative. Yes. uh during back in
uh 1999 2000 uh he lived in Queens and
that's how I got my first Taliban visa
to visit Afghanistan is I went and
basically haunted uh in his apartment
and waited for him to come around
because he wouldn't respond to my faxes
and uh and but the point is he was
officially a Taliban guy and when I
found out kind of like where he lived I
was asking around and the Chinese fruit
vendors were like oh yeah you'll know
him he's the one with the giant beard.
So
>> Alba is asking or not Alba, I'm sorry,
Magister Militum is asking if this is
the first time this has happened. The
answer is no. It happened during Reagan.
Reagan was very angry in this way as
well. And and Reagan banned the
Palestinians uh from coming.
>> But I mean, just to give you an idea of
of how absurd this is,
>> not only did Kaddafi come every year.
But he would ask permission to sleep in
a tent in Central Park.
>> Right.
>> Right. He's a man of the people. He's a
bedawin. He's going to sleep in the
tent. He's not comfortable sleeping in
the uh Ritz Carlton.
>> A luxury tent.
>> Right. A luxury tent without a doubt.
And then
>> he was he was the he was the OG glamper.
>> Yeah, he was. That was the invention of
glamping. and we would say, "No, you
can't stay in a tent in Central Park
because it's going to be impossible to
protect." And we would insist that he
stay in a hotel. And of course, he
would. That's as far as we would go with
this this short exception in like 19
1981 1982 where Reagan wouldn't allow
the Palestinians. Everybody is welcome.
And I'll tell you just as an aside, uh,
when I was assigned to the UN back in
whenever it was 2003, 2004,
um, the North Koreans don't have any
money. And so
most everybody lives in the five buraus.
A handful of foreign diplomats live in
New Jersey, but most for for most
Western diplomats, the rule was no
bridges, no tunnels. You had to live in
Manhattan.
The North Koreans have so little money.
They live on Roosevelt Island.
And one day I went over there thinking,
I wonder if I can find a North Korean.
Maybe I'll, you know, say hello and just
kind of accidentally bump into them.
Sure enough, here are all the North
Korean diplomats. And what are they
doing? They're fishing in the East River
for dinner.
For dinner. In the East River. probably
cleaner than any body of water in North
Korea.
>> It probably was.
>> That's true.
>> No one spoke English, so it didn't do me
any good anyway. But yeah, I learned
things are
>> Were they dressed funny?
>> Pardon?
>> Were they dressed funny? Like like weird
>> Yeah, they were clearly not Americans
and not new immigrants to the United
States. They were clearly North Korean.
Yes,
>> that's very very strange. I love that
story. So apparently from a practical
point of view, a lot of this is purely
symbolic because if you're a member of
the delegation because the Palestinian
Authority is an observer non- voting
member of the UN um they they can get an
exception an automatic exception to this
visa denial and obviously Marco Rubio
knows that. Um so the only person who
might be practically affected here is
Makmoud Abbas. Um and uh he might not be
able to come. This is obviously um one
of the uh one of the po posters here
wanted to ask and I I'm sorry that I
can't find their name. Wanted to know do
you think do we think that um any of the
countries like France will reneg on
their promise to recognize Palestine? I
would say no. There's no reason to
believe that.
>> I I agree except for Germany. Um
>> but they haven't said they would. They
haven't said they would. They said they
were considering it, but yeah, I think
the answer is no. Which which then puts
puts more pressure on Donald Trump than
it does on anybody else,
>> you know? I either way, I think
>> I agree. I think this is a bad I think
it's a bad move. In fact, I think
Trump's We're going to talk about other
stuff uh today that I think Trump is is
handling poorly from his own PR point of
view. You know, when you behave when you
when you lash out in anger
>> Yeah.
>> you tend to make mistakes.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And and this this looks to
me to be kind of a clear mistake.
>> So basically September is next week. Um
Trump is obviously knows he's about to
do you think he basically finally
focused on the general assembly and
started to think, "Oh my god, I'm going
to look like shit." And and it's
starting to piss him off.
I think something's pissing him off
>> because it's right in his own It's right
here in America. I mean, Vladimir Putin
just came to the United States.
>> Yes. Yes. And and look at it this way.
>> And there's an arrest warrant out for
him,
>> an international arrest warrant. And
look at it this way. What better
opportunity could there possibly be if
you are if you are
Nobel Peace Prize candidate uh Donald
Trump to force the Israelis and the
Palestinians to shake hands at the
United Nations General Assembly.
>> You know,
>> yeah. Well, not getting it, Ted. I I
don't I don't understand what the
endgame is supposed to be when you just
ban them from coming to an international
uh uh event.
>> Well, the and and you know, by the way,
so the State Department uh officials
statement uh says that uh you know, the
Palestinian Authority failed to
repudiate the October 7th Hamas raid. I
like to call it a raid because it's
really a raid. Um you know, is that
true? I'm not sure they have. I thought
they did say something about it at the
time.
>> I they I think they did.
>> So, you know, the the Hamas attack set
back the Palestinian cause
in the United States by years,
>> right?
>> Right. And has resulted in the deaths of
I think well over a 100,000 people
>> easily. Easily.
>> And
I honestly I just don't understand. I
don't see what it is that the United
States is trying to accomplish by this
move or that Israel thinks it's
accomplishing by encouraging the United
States to to take this move.
>> It doesn't sense to me.
>> Well, not to mention if there's any
future I mean, look, if there's going to
be a Palestinian partner, it's going to
be the Palestinian Authority. I mean, I
don't think it ought to be, but that's
from their point of view, that's that's
who they're going to choose. Um, so I I
agree with you. Um, firmware, thank you
very much for the donation. Uh, is
wondering what will happen with Israeli
Israel defenders when Israel ceases to
exist as a Jewish state. Seems to me
karma will make this inevitable.
>> Yeah,
>> I kind of agree with that and I think
we're going to probably live to see it,
John. I a big statement, but I think
they're so they're closing in so quickly
on pariah status. You know, yesterday
there was yesterday morning there was a
really blink and you miss it piece on
NPR uh talking about uh the difference
in the way that Israeli media covers
Gaza or doesn't cover Gaza and the way
that all other international media does
and how the Israelis are completely
isolated. They have no idea really
what's going what their people are doing
in Gaza because it's not covered and a
lot of them don't speak other languages.
So even if they decided to tune in to Al
Jazera or they wanted to tune in to uh
you know CNN International or BC BBC,
they wouldn't be able to uh they
wouldn't. So they're get all they hear
about is you know we're sending in tons
of food. The Hamas is stealing it. Um we
do everything we can to avoid civilian
casualties. Um you know the rest of the
world is lying about us. But they're
getting so much spin that they don't
really have any ability to like suddenly
they think the whole world is turning on
them just because they're a bunch of
like [__] anti-semites and that's not
what's going on.
>> I think that's exactly right. I have to
agree with with Rid that I'm not sure
that that is going to happen. I'm not
saying when that.
>> I'm not sure either. But but I do agree
that Israel is in many ways already a
pariah state. I think it will worsen its
own situation
>> and it's going to be tougher and tougher
and tougher for Israel to carry on
international diplomacy because they're
going to be countries formerly friendly
countries or ne neutral countries that
are not going to want to have anything
to do with it.
>> Yeah. And and no one's going to want to
do business with them either.
>> No way. Um, and yeah, it's just that's
just going to get worse and worse. Their
economy is going to be in real trouble.
>> And uh, yeah, I I don't see them coming
back from this. U at some point, look,
we need a one-stage solution. We need a
republic, a democratic republic of
Palestine, from the river to the sea
where no expulsions, but everybody
lives. Everybody gets one person, one
vote.
>> That's what needs to happen. And uh you
know ethnostates are a 20th century
construct. They don't have any place in
the modern era.
>> Yeah, I have to agree.
>> So
>> I have to agree. Yep.
>> Yeah. So I guess the thing is this is
going to have no real practical effect.
And and you know I got to say the other
thing is um when you're playing to to
international public opinion as Israel
and everybody is trying to do, you have
to come off as you're reasonable.
>> Yes. Right.
And like the Israelis don't come off
that way.
>> You know, you know who said that the
Israelis weren't reasonable?
>> Jimmy Carter said that
>> when they were negotiating um the Camp
David Accords, he said the thing about
the Israelis, he said it in in his the
first memoir after his presidency ended.
He said the Israelis will come into
negotiations with their bottom line.
They they lead with their bottom line
and then they won't budge from it.
>> So what's what's the point of a
negotiation?
>> Yeah. If you're not going to budge,
>> there's nothing right. No, exactly.
>> There's nothing to say.
>> And then take it or leave it. That's it.
>> Yeah. They can't live with They just
can't live with it. Um
>> Yeah. Uh question. Uh thanks Tariq for
the donation. Primo Lutu. Uh reference
to Louis the 14th.
>> Um yeah, I don't know. I think honestly
um he's already got Luj right now.
You know, BB Netanyahu has led. He is
the Zalinski of Israel. He has led he's
the Hitler of Israel in that he has led
his country to disaster. Um he has um he
is I mean this is a country that uh
could have survived this um and you know
just think if he had par if they had
parlayed uh you know they they rightly
called October 7th uh their 9/11 and it
was and imagine if after 911 the the
world the US had you know considered it
a police action and said you know and
said we want to we want to try the we
want to capture these guys put them on
trial at the Hague because it wasn't
just a crime against New York or
Washington or Shanksville, Pennsylvania.
It's a crime against the world. These
are terrorists. Al Qaeda has attacked
East Africa, Kenya and Tanzania and
other countries. We want to drag them,
put them on trial next, you know, same
way we did with Malloik. Put them there.
Um and then, you know, basically then
came out to the world and said,
>> "We're look, if we did something wrong
in our foreign policy, we want to hear
about it."
>> Yeah.
>> You know, we would have come off as
really reasonable. That's what Israel
should have. They should have learned
from us. They should have said after
October 7th like
>> this is a you know this is a police
situation. Everybody committed crimes we
want to put on trial fair trial
>> and treat it that way.
>> They would have they would have had
sympathy.
>> But the Israelis have never operated
that way. Never. I mean look at look at
Munich in 72. It took them 20 years, 30
years, 30 years to send teams of
assassins all around the world to shoot
and kill every single one of the
Palestinians that um that participated
in the attack on the Israeli Olympic
team in in uh Germany. They killed
innocent people,
>> right? By accident. They by accident
they killed innocent people. I guess it
was an accident, but it wasn't about
justice. It was about vengeance. It's
the same mistake that the CIA made after
911 where it wasn't about bringing
people to justice. It was about getting
revenge on the people who had
embarrassed the CIA because 9/11 was
such a great intelligence failure.
>> I also think it's a it's a Reichto fire
thing, right? Like um you know people
always think the Reichto fire was staged
by the Nazis. It wasn't. It was
organically what a Dutch anarchist. Um
but the it was an opportunity by you
know factions within the government like
hey we can use this for a crackdown.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean but the Israelis knew October 7th
was going to happen in exquisite detail.
I mean
they let it happen because they wanted
to use this as an excuse to get to grab
Gaza and maybe the West Bank too. I'm
convinced of it. I mean I don't see any
other way around it. I mean, I know it's
really it's extreme, but what they've
done is extreme and it it fits the
narrative. I mean, I I'll revisit it if
they if something changes and there's a
a a better model fits, but right now I'm
I'm going with that.
>> I think you're right. I think you're
right. I think this was a bad day for US
foreign policy, a bad day for diplomacy.
You know, every time there's an
opportunity for us to throw a wrench
into this notion that we're the honest
brokers in international diplomacy, we
throw the wrench. And we did it again
today.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, how can we with a straight face,
how can we look at any other country and
say, "No, we're not in bed with the
Israelis. We're independent."
>> Well, now we're not only in bed. We're
on the bottom.
>> Yeah. Yeah. We're bottoms. That's right.
>> That's right.
>> Got to say it. Um, all right. So, I
don't know do if we if we have more to
say about that, but we have other stuff
to talk about. So, but we can come back
to this. Um, oh, why wasn't the Iron
Dome working that day is a question from
uh CBR47.
Um, well, I mean, it's not an Iron Dome
issue. It's a smart fence issue, right?
I mean it the the f the fence was as
soon as that sec that fence was
breached. We all saw the video with the
bulldozer.
>> Um you know alarms went off in uh IDF HQ
in Tel Aviv and everywhere else and they
knew instantaneously right now accord
this blows my mind right but you could
look it up in the New York Times the
fastest response to a to any kabutz was
eight hours.
>> Yes.
>> The fastest. That's the that's the quick
one. That's like we're on it. We're
right there.
>> And don't forget
>> was 20
>> 20 hours. Don't forget that Israeli
settlers all up and down the the border
with Gaza,
Israeli settlers who are supposed to be
that the that first line of defense had
been warning the Israeli government for
two weeks that something was going on,
that there was a lot of chatter on the
radios that they hadn't heard before.
And the night before the the attack, the
Palestinians had sent kites um over the
over the fence. And Idomar Bengavir,
who has no business being in government,
he ought to be in prison like probably
for the rest of his life for hate
crimes,
>> um said, "No, there won't be a Gaza
attack. The attack is coming in the West
Bank." Call me cynical, but I think
that's what the plan was.
The plan was to pretend that the
Israelis didn't know or didn't believe
that the attack was coming from Gaza,
that it was coming from the West Bank.
And so they made themselves look like
they were unprepared.
>> But how could the attack have come from
the West Bank? That's that's that's the
Palestinian Authority. That's Fatah.
>> Exactly. Fata, that's on your payroll,
>> right? Those are your those are your
butt boys. They're not coming for you.
Somebody mentioned in the comments a
minute ago um that they just finished
watching Fauda. Um FA is a TV series and
is it's a joint Israeli Palestinian TV
series that I recommend at every
opportunity. I've talked about it on a
dozen different podcasts. I even
mentioned it on Fox News one night. Um
watch Fa on Netflix, F Auda. Watch it
and it will explain so much about the
relationship between the Israelis and
the PA and the Israelis and Hamas.
>> Oh yeah, and this is a good point.
Houdini points out that the Egyptians
told them it was going to happen. Yeah.
>> And the Egyptians told them it was going
to happen. That's right. Yes.
>> In detail.
>> Yep.
>> And and don't forget it was posted on
social media. This wasn't the vague, you
know, pre 911. Uh even, you know, I'm
not the nicest person to George W. Bush,
but I always thought it was unfair that
he got criticized for that um August
memo, you know, uh al Qaeda posed to po
uh posed to attack uh on US soil. That's
great. It's like, so John, um look out.
Look out for what, Ted?
>> Just look out. What are you supposed to
do with that?
>> Yeah. What do you do with that?
>> There's no details, right? But there
were plenty of details here. Um, thanks
for firmware for the $5 donation. Don't
forget
>> the plurality, if not majority of
Israeli civilians killed were by the IDF
using the Hannibal doctrine. Yeah. With
drones and other,
>> you know, and I wanted to I wanted to
add something
>> certainly a significant number.
>> Firmware's uh comment um that uh
that um what is firmware's comment? Oh
yeah. So, when I was in Greece in in
March, I was talking to a a Greek
journalist friend of mine, and he went
to Gaza on the 8th of October. Of
course, he had an Israeli military
handler, but he said they they drove
into Gaza, of course, and he said there
was this line of cars. He said there
were at least 50 cars, maybe more than
50 cars, and every one of the cars had
dead bodies in them, and all of the dead
were Israelis. But all of the cars had
large caliber holes in the roofs of the
car.
>> M
>> they had been shot from helicopters,
>> right?
>> And so my friend said to this Israeli
handler, "Wait a minute. Wait a What's
with all these dead bodies in the cars?
They were attacked clearly by air." And
the guy just said, "Don't worry about
those dead bodies." And that was it.
That was all he would say because every
single one of them had been killed by
the IDF and they were all Israelis that
were killed. All of them.
>> Right. Now,
>> now in some cases maybe I mean I guess
you could argue uh you know if if the
Israelis saw a car driven by a Hamas
fighter and they have a a hostage and
then they blow up the car and everybody
inside dies, that must have happened to
some extent.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it must have. It
must have.
>> It's It's heinous.
>> It is.
>> Um All right. Well, let's talk about
since we're talking about foreign
policy.
>> Trump has maybe you know more about this
than I do. Um I thought this was pretty
obscure, but the White House uh is
invoking something called a pocket
recision. They're cancelling uh nearly
$5 billion in congressionally approved
foreign aid. They're going after the
State Department and USAD. Although USA
ID effectively doesn't exist anymore,
>> so I guess that's sort of redundant. Uh
anyway, the last time this was done is
in 1977. Uh they're taking advantage of
the fact that the fiscal year ends in uh
just over 30 days, but there's only
there's a 45day review period. So
basically, Congress doesn't have enough
time to uh to exercise their
prerogatives to uh to to uh you know to
de basically So this money's already
been appropriated.
>> Yep.
>> Trump's deappropriating it basically
under the noses of Congress. Congress is
jealous of their prerogatives when it
comes to the matters of the purse.
Senate Appropriations Chairperson Susan
Collins is is pissed. Uh although you
know since when has she ever done
anything about being fisk um but anyway
she might as well be a Democrat in that
respect. U
>> anyway she says it's illegal under
something called the empoundment control
act. Uh Democrats say it's another Trump
power grab.
>> Yeah. It was my it was my impression
that this was illegal. This was
something that that was done in 1977. It
was tried again in 1993.
Republicans sued. It went to the Supreme
Court and the Supreme Court said, "No,
you can't do that." So Trump's doing it
again. Anyway, now the reason he may get
away with it this time is that
>> he's running out the clock. Yeah,
>> exactly.
Yeah, he's running out the clock.
>> Do we care?
>> Should we Should we care? I mean, a lot
of people look at foreign aid and think
that's money that we need here at home.
>> I'm glad you said that. I'm glad you
said that. I interviewed for my other
podcast. I interviewed John Perkins
today. He he's he wrote um a book called
Confessions of an Economic Hitman.
Wildly popular the third one. And I
asked him about this and um and he said
that
this is o of all of the the Trump
shortsighted policies, this one is the
most shortsighted because foreign aid is
not just handing bags of cash to foreign
leaders. Foreign aid is sending teams or
paying to send teams to, you know, dig
water wells or build a school or teach
new farming techniques or, you know,
building an electrical grid or whatever.
A lot of it lately has has been
associated with the development of green
energy, installing windmills, for
example, or solar panels. And now we're
not going to do that.
at all anywhere. This is what this is
what wonks call soft power.
>> Soft power. But the Chinese are going to
do it and the Chinese are doing it
>> ma in massive amounts. I mean it's
always seemed to be like US foreign US
soft power as I've seen it has always
seemed small and lame, right? Like I
remember walking around in uh in Central
Asia seeing like cans of rape seed oil.
Yeah.
>> That the US had donated. And I was like,
so at the same in the same exact place
where the Chinese were building a
highway and the chi and the and and the
and the highway says has a giant Chinese
flag, gifts from your brothers and the
people's republic of China. Uh and then
meanwhile we're giving them the rape
seed oil. I'm like,
>> uh, you know, it's it's pretty lame.
>> Not a lot. You're not gonna you're not
going to even you're not gonna be able
to buy any hearts and minds. You can't
even rent hearts and minds with rape
seed oil.
>> No, you can't. I'm sorry to change the
subject real quick, but Bob Oz is saying
that Dmitri Lascatis is being held for
questioning today by the CRI police on
the request of Israel.
>> So, who's who's Dimmitri Lascaris?
>> What the [__] Dimmitri is a um
he's a a journalist, a blogger,
a thinker on these on these issues. Let
me see if he has an actual title. I've
met him a couple times.
Here he is. A lawyer. He does all
different kinds of things. He's he's
frequently on um on um
Twitter or whatever we're calling
Twitter now.
>> Ex.
>> Yeah. Ex uh journalist. He he just calls
himself journalist and lawyer. Uh very
serious guy, activist.
um Canadian citizen I think uh yeah
University of Toronto Faculty of Law um
detaining him would be extraordinarily
provocative and at the at the request of
the Israelis. See this is this is a
problem that the Criates and the Greeks
have with the Israelis. The Greeks have
completely gotten into bed with the
Israelis and so have the Criates because
they share that giant gas field and they
don't want the Turks to take it. And
because the Israelis are involved,
that's the only reason the Turks haven't
taken it. And so in exchange, the
Israelis want the Greeks and the Criates
to do their bidding. And they are. So
now the Israelis say, "Oh, grab this
Greek Canadian guy. We don't like what's
coming out of his mouth." The Criates
actually do it. Sickening. I'm sorry to
hear that. That is really bad.
Really bad.
>> So, all right. We'll we'll follow up.
That's obviously a breaking news thing
that I'm very unfamiliar with. Um Yeah.
I don't understand exactly why uh why
why the uh Israelis still have are still
getting their calls returned at all.
>> Um Nadia Margaret is over on the uh on
the on the rumble on the Rumble chat is
saying that he brought lawsuits against
Israeli lobbies in Canada.
>> There you go. That is it. That will do
it.
>> The make his life as uncomfortable as
they can until he walks away.
Wow. Wow. Boy, that makes me angry.
>> Well, so speaking of let's get into uh
our riffing off our first story. Uh that
this struck me as pettiness, but it's a
little complicated. So, or I should say
not really complicated, but there's some
nuance to it. So, Trump uh cut off Kla
Harris's Secret Service protection.
>> Yeah. So mean-spirited. Oh,
>> now my that was my first reaction. And I
remember just thinking like if I were
advising the president, I would say you
don't want something to happen to her
after you do this. Nope.
>> I mean, if something happens to her,
that's going to be on you and it's going
to destroy you. I mean, you know, so
>> it's like when Biden wouldn't approve
Secret Service protection to Bobby
Kennedy Jr.
>> and then, you know, twice people got
>> Kennedy for K's sake.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And then a guy, an armed guy got into
the same ballroom that he was in in Los
Angeles and then two weeks later
somebody went over the fence at his uh
at his house in Santa Monica. So yeah,
you don't want to to take away Secret
Service protection and then have
something happen. It's a bad look. Now,
on the other hand, um the standard um so
so apparently uh it expired July 21st um
and there had been an undisclosed
18-month extension that Joe Biden had
already provided.
>> Yes.
>> So Biden extension.
>> So this will Yes. So this will so
basically she would have not had it
anyway. It's like so the question is
should it have been extended? Should the
Biden extension have been allowed to
remain in place?
I mean, I feel like honestly I'm
surprised it's so short. I mean, seems
to me like,
>> yeah,
>> you should be I mean, I think if you
were a major candidate for for president
and you want you want it, you should be
able to have it for the rest of your
life.
>> I mean, does anybody really want to kill
Dan Quail?
>> Um,
>> probably not. But and and he probably
doesn't want that that level of
security, right?
>> You know, I I think I've told you when
George McGovern um announced his
candidacy for president in 1984, I
introduced him. It was the proudest day
of my life as a as a college student to
have the former Democratic nominee for
president of the United States call me
as the as the head of the college
Democrats at George Washington
University and say, "I want to announce
my candidacy. Can you set it up for me?"
I was like, "Oh my god." And then I
started volunteering at the at the
McGovern campaign. Well, just after he
announced, I remember on ABC News, they
showed clips of him from 1972
speaking to crowds of, you know, 40,000,
50,000 people at a time in stadiums,
being mobbed at airports, people wanting
to take pictures with him and get his
autograph. And then they showed him in
1984 walking through Reagan National
Airport. It was it was National Airport
at the time and not a single person
recognized him.
>> That's crazy.
>> Not a single person.
>> Um
>> so no, I don't think I don't think we
should give it to them for life. Um but
but six months
>> seems short.
>> Yeah. Six months after a contentious
election where she was the first black
woman ever to be nominated for
president,
>> right?
>> Yeah. You might want to make it longer
than six months. It just seems
mean-spirited to me to to
>> and again because she already had it for
18 months, it's kind of like taking it
away. It's like putting a target on her
back. Um
>> yeah, it is. And and I want to thank
Matthew Blair Reigns. I'm sorry. Before
you go to an ad, uh thank you very much
for the five pounds. Is Trump a true
aberration in US history? So far, I
think yes, this is an aberration. But
with that said,
populism is attractive to a lot of
people. In this case, right-wing
populism. Um, there's nobody out there
right now as popular as Donald Trump is.
That could change in the next couple of
years. I think it probably won't, which
would mean then that he was an
aberration. But I think the juryy's
still out. What do you think, Ted?
>> Well, I mean, I think generally you're
right, certainly in the modern era. But
I do, you know, you know who his
favorite president is? Andrew Jackson.
>> Andrew Jackson.
>> And you know this Andrew Jackson was a
nut.
>> He was killer.
>> Yeah, he was. He was a wild man. I mean,
I don't even know where to start with
that guy, but he liked to he loved to
duel, which was frowned upon at the
time. And he he liked to [__] other guys
wives and then and then and then mix it
up with them, you know, on the d while
dueling. He remember his inauguration.
He invited the people into the White
House to party and all of his all of his
supporters were a bunch of Repscallions.
They trashed the place. They stole the
the the plates. Uh the place, you know,
it had to be renovated after they were
done.
>> It's embarrassing.
>> He not to mention Oh, and he tanked the
economy like like crazy.
>> In fact, there was a depression that he
oversaw. It was so bad that m that
literally the government couldn't afford
to to mint coins anymore. People had to
create their own fake coins in order to
circulate. It's called they're called
hard times tokens. They're highly
collectible.
>> They're very collectible and
>> and they're very cool and interesting.
Um let me read this ad. Uh okay. Set
your clocks, mark your calendars, and
buckle up for the best NFL prime town
prime time football action starting
September 4th on Westwood 1. You can
catch all the bone crushing hits, last
second heroics, and edgeofyour seat
action that NFL Thursday, Sunday, and
Monday nights have to offer. Whether
you're tailgating, driving, or chilling
at home. Don't miss a single snap.
Listen on the NFL app, the Westwood One
Sports app at westwoodsports.com.
Or just say, "Alexa, open Westwood
Sports." If it's the NFL, it's on
Westwood One. So, yeah. No, Andrew
Jackson. Oh, Florida. You know, I love
that story.
>> Florida. Oh my god. under the doctrine
that it's easier to uh it's easier to
beg forgiveness than to get permission.
Um he basically was like told by
Congress didn't want to pick a war with
span with Spain which owned the what was
then called the Florida and and but but
Andrew Jackson as a general wanted it.
So he's like [__] it. So he disobeyed
Congress went in overthrew the Spaniards
and took and and defeated them. Right?
>> Congress is pissed. They call him on the
carpet. Get your ass to Washington for a
hearing. His defense is listen, they the
Spanish couldn't defend it and another
foreign power like say the Brits could
have come there, toppled the Spanish
because they had a a very poor force and
then we would have been [__] Well,
and I can prove that because I defeated
the Spanish. Therefore,
if I could defeat the Spanish, anyone
could defeat the Spanish. I proved my
point. You're welcome. And now Florida's
a state.
>> It's so American. It's beautifully
American.
>> So, I mean, I don't know. Is that I
mean, is Trump worse than Andrew
Jackson? I think he's kind of like in
the same vein.
>> Yeah. I think he's in the same vein.
He'll do something and then just say,
"What are you going to do about it? Sue
me."
>> Yeah. You and what army?
>> Yeah. Exactly.
Exactly.
>> Um nuts. So, by the way, um she's about
to Kamla is about to go on book tour. Uh
and Governor Gavin Newsome and LA Mayor
Karen Bass, who can't keep her own city
safe, uh but she's pledging that local
law enforcement will provide security at
her events.
>> Yeah, I'm sure that that's true.
>> Yeah, I'm sure that that And this is the
other thing, too. They were talking
about it on the morning shows today.
She's just now coming out with a
ghostritten uh autobiography. And so
she's just ready to start the book tour.
So she's going to be out there in public
constantly over the next, say, four
weeks. He He did this on purpose.
>> So this is just about It's just about
[__] with her.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> A troll.
>> Absolutely. Uh on purpose. Yes. It's a
It's a major troll. You're right.
>> That's what he is.
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah.
>> That's And that's And that's what this
um that's what this Palestinian thing
is, too. It's basically like, "Oh, the
Palestinians are going to have their
parade.
>> I'm going to rain on their parade."
That's all it is.
>> But you know what, Ted? I think this
makes us weaker
>> as as a country. It makes us weaker.
There are a lot of Palestinians in the
United States, especially in in Michigan
and New Jersey and New York. Um, if, as
I said earlier, if we want to appear to
be the honest broker, which we're not,
but we like to appear that we are, this
is exactly the opposite of what he
should be doing. And it's like he just
did it in a fit of peak without uh
thinking it through. It doesn't make any
sense to me.
>> John, question for you from Two Toes on
YouTube. Uh, did you see Bamante's
recent interview on Diary of a CEO? It
was detailing his new book that's about
a mission he did to hunt out a mole
within the CIA. I'm just not how sure
how much I buy of it. He says,
>> "No, I didn't see it." Funny that he was
on Diary of a CEO. They just invited me
yesterday to come on Diary of a CEO. Um,
listen, Bamante is a nice enough guy,
but Bamante was what was called a sue, a
special operations officer. He was not a
case officer. He was certainly not a
mole hunter. Right? There's a unit at
the CIA that's within the
counterintelligence center. They are the
mole hunters and they work handinand
glove with the FBI's National Security
Division. What a special operations
officer does quite literally
is when John is preparing to meet with a
sensitive source, I'll say, "Hey,
Andrew, put together a counter
surveillance team for me and provide
protection tonight when I go out from my
meeting." or when I come back from the
meeting, hey Andrew, I have a lot of
stuff to write up, so do me a favor and
do my paperwork for me for for finance
because I'm too busy. So, here are my
receipts. That's what a special
operations officer does. He's not a mole
hunter. He's not a case officer. He's
not recruiting spies to steal secrets.
He's not a targeting officer trying to
find Osama bin Laden. He's an assistant.
Sorry, I have to be so He's a gopher.
>> Oh my god. Now I'm gonna go I'm gonna
have to go back and find that because I
I want to see it. That's That's too
much. Oh my god.
>> Uh no. And answering S347. I didn't hear
anything about what Al Sharpton had to
say about the National Guard in Chicago,
Memphis, and Minneapolis. But I'd like
to hear
>> I'd like to hear it. I have
special disdain for Al Sharpton. special
disdain. Sorry, but I'm still mad about
the whole Toana Broly thing. Google
>> if you don't know it. One of the guys
that whose life he ruined was a Greek
American.
>> He was a state trooper, wasn't he?
>> That's right. He was a state trooper of
New York State Police, Tana Broly, who
so took it on the chin for her lies that
she had to change her name and move to
Washington.
Sickening.
>> Yeah. You know that that was a uh that
was a a very very sorted affair and uh
>> sure was.
>> I mean I guess in America everyone can
rein uh can reinvent themselves. Tariq
wants to know is there stolen valor in
the agency?
>> You know I um
yes there is. I've tried not to use that
term because I'm trying not to call him
out so directly, but uh yeah.
>> Yes.
>> Just yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Just Yeah. Sometimes just yeah is
enough.
>> Oh, listen. Let me add one thing,
>> please.
>> I I love Julian Dory, the podcaster.
I've been on his podcast a couple times.
He is an absolutely outstanding
interviewer. Um he and Buspante are
friends. And Julian texted me. This is
about two months ago. He said, "Hey,
don't tell anybody, but I'm gonna be
waterboarded on camera so people can see
what actual waterboarding is." I'm like,
"Oh,
>> that's like that's like what uh
Christopher Hitchens did."
>> Yes, it's exactly what Christopher
Hitchens did. I said, "Cool." I said,
"It's it's awful. We waterboarded each
other in in training and it's terrible."
So he sends me the video um before he
released it and it's Bamante
waterboarding him, but rather than you
know laying on a board strapped to a
board with cloth in your mouth and
having the water poured on your face,
he's sitting on a bench with his head
down like that and Bamante's pouring
water on his head.
>> Well, that's that's like the service you
get in the Turkish baths.
>> Exactly. You pay good money for that.
>> I pay money for that. And maybe you get
a little massage on top of it.
>> Sure. Shampoo.
>> Yeah. But come on, man. I This guy.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Abby Mari, he wants to be an
influencer so bad. Isn't that the truth?
Oh my god.
>> If I ever become president, I promise to
ban the word influencer. And all people
who are influencers or purport to be
influencers, I'll put it in the
constitution. Pedro, Pedro Luis Taff,
I'm I'm glad somebody raised this
because frankly I forgot. Um, what about
the news about Tulsi Gabbard and the CIA
name? Did we talk about this yesterday?
>> No, we didn't.
>> Oh, well, last week when Tulsi Gabbard
fired 37 CIA Russia analysts.
>> Um, she she went on Twitter and said, "I
fired these 37 people."
>> Oh, right, right. We did talk about
this.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, not her name. She burned.
Yeah, she burned an agent.
>> She burned a woman who's undercover.
>> Well, that's a violation of the
Intelligence Identities Protection Act
of 1982.
And I was the second person in American
history um charged with violating the
Intelligence Identities Protection Act
of 1982. So, what do you do? I mean,
Tulsi is not going to be charged with a
crime, let alone a felony. Um,
>> no, she won't say. No, it's it's it's
No, it's it's it's got to drive you
completely insane. It would me. Uh, no
doubt about it. Uh, by the way, Lurley
says Hitchens gets some credit. He
changed his tune after going through it.
Yeah, that's right. I watched the video.
It's on It's still on YouTube. Um, you
basically, you know, Hitch was a, you
know, he he he pissed me off so bad
because he seemed like a good lefty and
then went crazy after 911 and basically
went full spectrum, you know, is
Islamopascism. He popularized the term
and all.
>> You remember that term? And it didn't
catch on.
>> It's so nonsensical. It is.
But anyway, he uh but then he was just
like, you know, we have to kind of like
Bill Maher. All these people kind of
like went crazy and uh he was like
talking about ah you torture,
what's the big deal about waterboarding?
So just so he agreed to undergo the
procedure uh and just to see what it was
like. Not only did he he find it
extremely upsetting, but he had PTSD as
a result of it the rest of his life.
>> Um, he had he required psychological
treatment. Uh, and he never stopped
evangelizing against here. He reminds me
of a of a guy who Anyway, I know a guy
who like was used to be far right, then
he went became far left and then he
became far right again. It's just like,
dude, you got to just relax. He claimed
to have been actually either CIA or
something, but I I don't you know, he he
claimed to be a wet ops guy going back
to the Congo War.
>> No, no, no. Nobody in the CIA would ever
ever speak those word wet ops or black
ops. Those are straight out of the
movies. That's that's one of the ways
that I can I can sort of nail people who
are phonies.
I always I always suspected, but you
know,
>> wet ops, black ops, and the company
>> all from books
>> and and and bad Hollywood movies. Yes.
>> Um, Adam Fighter wants to know, we're
big leftists. You you guys are big
leftists. Have you heard of Hassan
Piper?
>> No, I haven't.
>> Not me, but you can tell us who who that
is.
Um,
Pedro says, "There seems to be a lot of
there seem to be XCIA people trying to
be influencers now." Tracy Walder is
another famous one.
>> Oh, yeah. That's absolutely true. That's
ab Hassan [__] is a Turkish American
online streamer, YouTuber, influencer,
and left-wing political commentator.
>> That sounds interesting. I'll check him
out. He's young. He's 34. He's 6'4, Ted.
So, he's even taller than you are.
>> What? That's not fair. No one should be
>> His streams typically consist of
political and social commentary, gaming,
and media consumption. We should have
him on the show.
>> Sure, why not? Robbie, you're you're
listening. Please invite him or just
remind me to invite him or whatever.
We'll take care of it. Um Oh, yeah.
Tariq wants to know this is I'm glad
that Tariq brought this up. We got to
touch base about naval movements in
Venezuela. Things are heating up down
there.
>> You know, we should talk about that,
Ted. That slipped my mind that there
there was some disagreement in the media
yesterday and today about what exactly
the point is. Is the point to frighten
the Venezuelans? Is the point to invade
Venezuela?
>> Um or is this just a dumb way to waste
money on naval resources?
>> I don't know.
>> Question.
>> Um it seems I I think it's saber. It's
the usual Saber Bradley. I don't think
Trump has the appetite to invade
Venezuela.
>> No. No, I don't either.
>> Uh,
>> you never have an exit strategy anyway.
It's easy to invade a country. It is
crazy difficult to occupy it and and
pull out.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's it's true. Um, and you
know, and the Venezuelans are very
nationalistic. Uh, they might hate each
other, but they would hate an invasion
force more. kind of like the Afghans, I
think. Um, do you think the two-party
system is poisonous in today's America?
Swerzy wants
to know.
>> Uh, I'm responding real quickly to
apparently Hassan [__] doesn't like me.
So, I'll
>> Well, then we don't like Hassan [__]
>> I was nephew. You know, his mother. I
just looked.
Thank you for the insanely amazingly
generous
>> $200 donation. Thank you so much.
>> Thank you.
>> Minus a penny,
>> but I won't I won't quibble about the
penny. No, seriously. Thank you so so so
so much. Um
>> really appreciate that.
>> Yeah.
>> So So Hassan Piker's mother mother's
maiden name is Waguer and I wondered if
he was related to Chen Wager. Michael
Gardner's telling us that he's Czech
Wigger's nephew. It's funny. Cheng
Waguer has never really been a friend of
mine either.
>> Yeah.
>> When I The first time I ever like I ever
did anything that got the second thing I
ever did that got wide press coverage
after blowing the whistle. Um it was my
it was my open letter to uh to my
supporters from prison that became my
first letter from Lorettto. And um
people just went crazy over it. I mean,
that's when that's when um
uh Oh my god, what's the matter with me?
came from CNN that we interviewed. Um
Ted,
>> who who did we interview from CNN?
>> Oh, uh Jake Tapper.
>> Jake Tapper. Thanks. That's when Jake
Tapper came to uh to the prison to
interview me. Uh
the the the response was universally
positive and interested except for Chank
Wiger.
Chen Weaguer just for 30 minutes just
ripped me.
>> And I never understood that because back
then, you know, I I probably agreed on
95% of the issues with Chen Weaguer.
Like, why is he attacking me like this?
But it's just as
>> I I've never been able to draw a bead on
on Chen Weaguer. I mean, I wanted to I I
kind of felt like I should have been
friends with him. He's one of those
guys. It's like an unrequited bromance
where you're sort of like you reach out,
you're like, "We should be buds. We
agree about a lot of stuff and then, you
know, they never call, they never write,
and then like they never and you know, I
noticed his uh deafening silence during
while everyone else was talking about
the LA Times. I couldn't help but notice
his deafening silence." Um, so
>> yeah.
>> Yes.
>> I don't know. I don't I I honestly don't
even get him like what he what he wants,
you know, what he's about, what he's
trying to do.
>> I don't get it either. I don't
understand. I don't understand. And I'll
tell you, he doesn't have very many
friends on the left. He He's very good
at u at pissing people off. Uh Nadia
Margaret, thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> Yes. And uh also um let's see here. Uh,
we've got like a Did Oh, Frameataz wants
to know, "Did we hear that the US is
evacuating bases in Iraq?"
>> Yes.
>> And Russia has yanked its diplomats from
Tel Aviv.
>> Tel Aviv. That's That's true. Um, I
heard it first from Doug McGregor and
then I heard it today from an Iranian
friend of mine.
>> What's the Russia thing about?
He was my friend was speculating that
it was a coincidence and I was like I
don't know man you know we're not privy
to these classified communications
>> and there may be something out there
that just hasn't leaked to the press and
it it could be if if we're to believe
parsy and I actually do believe parsy
that another Israeli attack on Iran is
coming. You know I heard something today
that was very interesting. I heard it
this the second time I heard it. So I
don't know if it's circular reporting if
there's something to it that Trump
actually did not want to attack Iran,
but Netanyahu told him that the threat
really was existential and that the
Israelis were going to use a nuclear
weapon, a tactical nuclear weapon. And
then Trump stepped in and said, "All
right, we'll use the 30,000 pound bomb.
You keep your nukes to yourself and
that's why we bombed." If true, that's
absolutely insane.
>> I I thought so too. But this
people are arguing now is kind of an
extension of that where the Israelis are
saying the threat is still existential.
It's still out there. We haven't
overthrown the Iranian regime. We have
to attack again. And so the Russians are
saying, "Okay, we're out of here." And
then the Americans are saying, "We're
going to shut down these bases. We don't
really need them anyway, and we want to
get our people out of the region." I
don't know. I'm speculating. I have no
idea if that's true.
>> One last topic and plus whatever people
in the chat. I mean, it is Friday, so uh
you know, but we always answer all the
questions. Um I love I wanted to throw
this one at you because I thought it was
cool. University of Burn um has a new
study out where basically they found
they have a theory for how life
developed on Earth. Um apparently up
until 4 billion years ago uh the earth
the proto earth was just a dry rock
incapable of supporting life. Then uh
another protolanet about the size of
Mars now they call it thea uh ran
smashed into the earth and it delivered
hydrogen, carbon and sulfur from outside
of the solar system. Um they're
analyzing uh meteorite isotopes and
manganese to chromium decay timelines
from the first 15 million years of
earth's formation, right? Like the
universe is about 17.6 uh uh billion
years old or something like that. So
this is a this is a a drop in the
bucket, right? But basically they they
find that there's there's a strong case
that all of these stuff that the stuff
that's in the earth would never have
been here if not for this sort of
cataclysmic
you know catastrophe
>> um at at one point in our in our uh you
know astronomical history. I don't know.
I think it's really cool. I think
astrophysics is really cool. You know, I
I missed this whole story until you sent
it uh to me, and I thought it was
absolutely fascinating.
>> I mean, these guys know so much more
than we do. And the way they lay out the
argument, it's it's entirely plausible.
>> Fascinating. And like you know I mean
and so basically it's like you know uh
it does sort of to me suggest the
possibility of life on in other parts of
the universe just because if certain
things smash into each other and you get
water and you get heat life might
happen. Right. It's like the lake the
bottom of Lake Bal kind of effect.
>> Exactly right. Yep. Yep. Fascinating.
>> Totally totally cool. Tom asks the right
question. Do you guys believe in God?
job.
>> Yeah, I do. I do. Um I used to never
miss a Sunday. Now I'm less reliable,
but uh Yeah, sure. I do.
>> And I do not.
>> Um I'd like to I used to I I grew up
Catholic.
>> I served mass. Nobody No priests ever
didd me. Um I don't know. Maybe I was
ugly,
but
it's like what? It's like I had a friend
I had a friend who came we from high
school. We got to be friends again like
20 years uh 20 years later he moves to
New York, right? And we're hanging out
drinking and he comes out to me and he
goes, "Oh, by the way, you should just
know like you know I'm by and and he
goes, "But don't worry, I'm not
attracted to you."
>> Oh, thanks a lot.
>> That's what I said. I said, "What am I,
Chopl?" It's like I'm like, "You'll [__]
anyone but not me."
>> My best friend, my best friend from
childhood. We've been friends since we
were five and we're in each other's
weddings and everything. So,
there were five of us that that are all
the, you know, close and we're all in
each other's weddings. We're all
godfather to each other's uh kids. So,
another friend of ours said, "Oh, I saw
so and so at the grocery store in
Pittsburgh, one of our one of my closest
friends, and he's holding hands with a
guy."
>> And I was like, "Oh, okay." So I said to
my best friend in the summer, this is
the summer of 95. I was just back from
Bahrain for RNR and I said, "What do you
think about our mutual friend? You think
he's gay?" Because if he is, I wish he
would just say it so we can say, "Dude,
we don't care if you're gay. We still
love you. There's no, it makes no
difference." And my buddy says to me, I
don't know if he's gay, but I sure know
I am. And I looked at him like
and I said
I said
>> surprise
>> you had sex with half the girls in high
school,
>> right?
>> He said I had sex with half the boys in
high school.
>> Oh, that's awesome.
>> I'm just looking at him. I got And then
I said, "Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
How many times have we shared a bed over
the years? What? I'm not good enough for
you."
>> Exactly. and he said, "I was never
attracted to you."
>> What's wrong with me?
>> I got the double whammy today.
>> That's That's awesome.
>> Oh my god. And he and his husband now
have been together for 30
Yeah. 31 years.
>> I had a I had a friend in a friend high
school friend uh who who stole my
girlfriend Megan from me.
>> And and and so like you know and and so
years later uh you know I read about
him. He was a a very accomplished
attorney in uh in in Cincinnati. He
worked on the Maple Thor case. Um I read
about him in the New York Times. Um and
so we got back I was like so I got was
really excited to get back in touch with
him. I was like congratulations you're
doing you know yman's work out there
fighting the right-wingers and we're
talking and I said and finally I was
like you know I got to call you out. Uh
you know and I go you're gay now I read
in the paper. And he goes, "Yeah." And I
go, "But you you stole Megan from me.
You stole my girlfriend. You [__] my
girlfriend." And he goes, "Dude, I did
you a favor. Why do you think I'm gay?
If you if you stayed with Megan, you'd
be gay. I fell on the grenade for you."
Oh my god. Hey, but I know I know we're
over time and I apologize, but we we
have a question and I want to say thank
you to uh USC A-Rod 21. Thanks for the
for the $10. What do we think about the
furer sending people to Chicago? He's a
resident and worries for the local
police. I'm going to say based on our
experience in Washington, uh, they're
just going to stand around in the
tourist areas and do nothing except
write tickets for people not wearing a
seat belt.
>> Yeah.
>> Dangerous places.
>> My friend Scott Stantis from the Chicago
Tribune told me just this morning, he
said they're going to stand around on on
the Magnificent Mile.
>> Exactly.
>> Um, and and have pictures taken. That's
it. He said he he said like, "Oh, they'd
be very welcome in the south side of
Chicago. The people would throw flowers
at them, but they're not going to go
there."
>> Nope. Nope. Um, there is breaking news.
Robbie's reminding us of I just I just
saw it. Robbie, is it about uh tariffs?
Uh, an appeals court, not a district
court, but a federal appellet court has
just ruled Donald Trump's tariffs
unconstitutional.
I don't know how that can be. I'm not a
lawyer, but
maybe
>> that's bizarre.
>> What you will of that? I thought so,
too.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Well, we'll see what happens
there.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So, uh, by the way, I just want to
point out in the chats here, um, Furer
was misspelled and we're talking F, we
were talking Fur O R, not the former
chancellor of Germany.
But anyway, all right, guys. Thank you
so much. We could do this all night
long, but you guys have lives, but we
might have lives, I guess. Um, thank you
so much. Please like, follow, and share
the show. Thank you for your generous
donations, especially that one. Oh my
god, that was amazing. Um, we will be
back. Uh, well, no, we're taking Monday
is a holiday, right?
>> Holiday.
>> Yeah, we take we take we take here on
the drogram show, we take federal
holidays off. So we will be back on
Tuesday uh which at 5:00 p p.m. Eastern
time Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday,
Friday of next week. We will see you
then. Looking forward to it. John, as
always a pleasure.
>> Take care everyone. Thank you everyone.